[{"answer": "He amuses me. I don't know of anything more amusing. Outside of this jigsaw puzzle. Don't you find it so, my friend", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Have you ever been in love", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " But I think we should talk about it. Or are you fully convinced that we too won't understand each other", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "In this case, getting married means nothing. Aren't we already the same as being married? And my friend and my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " It must have been around four or five..", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No... in the morning. Why? What's happened", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "But why don't you tell him?  A girl who was with us has disappeared", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, she didn't drown... She just disappeared, and nobody knows where", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I was saying... it might even be possible that my friend had left with them", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Listen, Marshal... As for there being reasons for going away, anyone of us might have three thousand of them. So you can assume that she had them. What I want to know, is it possible that the smugglers might have taken her aboard", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Have you any instructions for me, Lieutenant? May I return to my friend", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I left it at the warehouse", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Have you read it?... They're asking for anyone with information to get in touch with them", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yes, you should go", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "We have a radio like this, too", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "And why wouldn't we have one like this", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yes, but why do you think our readers would be interested in such news now? Even if I sent it, the editors wouldn't print it", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Pardon me, but why must I do you a favor", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "But why me?... Ask my friend, she's much more beautiful than me", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I appeal to you more", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend... I'm so ashamed of myself, so ashamed...I tried to hide myself...I feel so small... I hate myself ..", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh no... It doesn't please me at all..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend, let's get married", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes. We'll get married. You and I. What do you say", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes. We'll get married. You and I. What do you say", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You look at me as though I had said something foolish..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend..", "docId": "Avventura_-L_-(The-Adventure).txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Nothing, nothing  at all. I was just looking for my friend", "qsentId": 28}]